ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files
1986-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brown, Nellie
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
/4283/002
55.11 cubic feet
41.1 linear ft.
Records.
9250167
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D Cohen, April 19, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, April 20, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
Brown, Nellie; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension and Public Service Division
9250167
- CHIP Program #318, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1/09/91
- No. 338: MRC Bearings, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Folder 1 of 3
- No. 338: MRC Bearings, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Folder 2 of 3
- No. 338: MRC Bearings, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Folder 3 of 3
- No. 751: ALOSH/Jefferson School, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- No. 751: ALOSH/Jefferson School, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- No. 751: ALOSH/Jefferson School, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CHIP Program #921, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CHIP Program #930, 1975-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Client: Norman A. Palmiere, Esq., Title: V. Caiazza
- CHIP Program #953, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Client: ROCOSH/TA, Title: IAQ, Date: 4/23/93
- CHIP Program #955, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Client: Stockpole Corp., Title: Bruce C. Young, Date: 7/13/93
- CHIP Program #986, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Client: K. Hulslander, Esq., Title: Zaffarano v. Cincinnati Milacron, Date: 1/08/93
- CHIP Program #998, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Client: W. Seneca E. H.S., Title: JAQ
- CHIP Program #992, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Client: Corning Schools/NYSUT, Title: IAQ Tech. Asst., Date: 12/03/92
- CHIP Program #997, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Client: Sweet Home School District, Title: Prod. Subst., Date: 07/93
- CHIP Program #1084, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Client: WNYCOSH/Letchworth Schools, Title: IAQ Tech. Asst., Date: 3/28/94
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Folder 1 of 7
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Folder 2 of 7
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Folder 3 of 7
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Folder 4 of 7
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Folder 5 of 7
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Folder 6 of 7
- No. 1086: Schlenker v. FMC, 1991-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Folder 7 of 7
- No. 1096: Paul Beltz (was No. 794), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Folder 1 of 6
- No. 1096: Paul Beltz (was No. 794), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Folder 2 of 6
- No. 1096: Paul Beltz (was No. 794), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Folder 3 of 6
- No. 1096: Paul Beltz (was No. 794), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Folder 4 of 6
- No. 1096: Paul Beltz (was No. 794), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Folder 5 of 6
- No. 1096: Paul Beltz (was No. 794), 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Folder 6 of 6
- Tech Asst: Paul Beltz (Craig Watson), 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  98C1097, 4/24/94; 7/16/97; 2/27/98; 3/5/98; 3/13/98, Brown
- CHIP Program #1106, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Client: ALCOSH/NYSUT, Title: IAQ, Date: 6/02/94
- CHIP Program #1119, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Client: Good NBR Cmte.
- CHIP Program #1201, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Client: ROCOSH (IAQ), Title: Corning School and NYSUT, Date: 03/27/95
- CHIP Program #1203, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Client: ALCOSH, Date: 03/10/95
- CHIP Program #1205, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Client: WNYCOSH/NYSUT Potters School (W. Seneca), Title: IAQ, Date: 2/28/95
- CHIP Program #1208, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Client: WNYCOSH/NYSUT/Royalton Jr/Sr H.S., Title: IAQ Tech. Asst., Date: 3/14/95
- UFCW, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- CHIP Program #1244, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Client: Dover School District (Wingdale Elem), Title: IAQ, Date: 4/25/95
- CHIP Program #1249, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Client: ROCOSH/CSBA, Title: IAQ/CCFL, Date: 05/05/95
- No. 1251: SUNY Fredonia, 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Folder 1 of 2
- No. 1251: SUNY Fredonia, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Folder 2 of 2
- CHIP Program #1255, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: IAQ/LCMH, 6/01/95
- CHIP Program #1256, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Client: Catt. Cty./CSEA/ALCOSH, Title: IAQ, Date: 08/21/95
- CHIP Program #1263, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Client: Tom Green Elem. School, Title: Tech. Asst., Date: 8/10/95
- CHIP Program #1311, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Client: ALCOSH, Title: IAQ for Westfield School, Date: 10/18/95
- CHIP Program #1328, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Client: C. Watson, Esq., Title: W.M. White, Date: 11/27/95
- CHIP Program #1342, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: Tech. Asst., Date: 02/02/96
- CHIP Program #1343, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Client: Roch., Title: Charlotte Middle School
- CHIP Program #1349, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Client: Barker Schools, Title: IAQ- Tech. Asst., Date: 03/19/96
- CHIP Program #1353, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Client: UFCW Local #1, Title: IAQ, Date: 04/12/96
- CHIP Program #1355, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Client: ALCOSH/Rogers School, Title: Breast Cancer, Date: 5/7/96
- CHIP Program #1357, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: WNYCOSH, Vesuvius, USWA, Date: 11/13/96
- CHIP Program #1363, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Client: Trek and GCC, Title: PPE, Date: 06/12/96
- CHIP Program #1368, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Client: Carrier Corp, Title: Metalworking, Date: 06/96
- CHIP Program #1369, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Client: ALCOSH/Short and Smith Ins. Agency, Title: IAQ Tech. Asst., Date: 08/96
- No. 1372: Wall v. NYS, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Folder 1 of 4
- No. 1372: Wall v. NYS, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Folder 2 of 4
- No. 1372: Wall v. NYS, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Folder 3 of 4
- No. 1372: Wall v. NYS, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Folder 4 of 4
- CHIP Program #1397, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: IAQ/Village of Lewistown, Date: 10/25/1996
- CHIP Program #1404, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Client: NYSDOT, Title: IAQ, Date: 1/7/97
- CHIP Program #1412, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Client: T. Giordano, Esq., Title: J. Harvey, Date: 10/96
- No. 1410: Carrier Corporation, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- No. 1410: Carrier Corporation, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- CHIP Program #1419, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Client: NYSPEF, Title: IAQ Tech. Asst., Date: 3/18/97
- CHIP Program #1446, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Client: Genesis Chemicals
- CHIP Program #1447, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Client: Alden Schools, Title: Asbestos, Date: 06/09/97
- CHIP Program #1572, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: IAQ; West Seneca W. Sr. H.S., Date: 09/19/97
- CHIP Program #1573, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Client: UFCW, Title: Tech. Asst.-VDT's, Date: 09/25/97
- CHIP Program #1583, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Client: NYCOSH, Title: IAQ Site Visit
- CHIP Program #1584, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Client: Francis Amendola, Esq.
- CHIP Program #1591, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Client: Trek, Title: Tech. Asst.-Ventil., Date: 11/24/97
- CHIP Program #1592, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Client: Wilson School District, Title: IAQ Investig., Date: 02/23/98
- CHIP Program #1593, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Client: NYSUT, Title: IAQ, Date: 03/30/98
- CHIP Program #1622, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Client: Joseph Krenitsky, Title: Tech. Asst., Date: 11/1/98
- CHIP Program #1643, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: Tech. Asst. for Almco. Props., Date: 02/12/98
- CHIP Program #1645, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Client: UFCW, Title: Bakery Oven Decomp.
- CHIP Program #1653, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Client: WNYCOSH, Title: IAQ Report Review, Date: 04/07/98
- CHIP Program #1704, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Client: Town of Grand Island, Title: IAQ Tech. Asst., Date: 07/06/98
- Tech. Asst.: Measurement of Magnetic Fields, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  99C1707; Trek, Inc.; Site Visit; Brown; 7/8/99
- CHIP Program #1712, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Client: UFCW, Title: VDT Workstations, Date: 08/19/98
- Tech. Assist: Stakeholder Buy-in Mtg., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH Indoor Air Quality-Wilson Central; 99C1713 (a); Brown; 1/11/99
- Tech. Assist.-Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH-Tools for Schools (Data Analysis) Wilson; 99C1713 (B); Brown; 4/21/99
- Tech. Assist.: Write Technical Rot., 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH Indoor Air Quality-Wilson Central; 99C1713 (c)
- Tech. Assist.-Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH-Tools for Schools (Follow-up) Wilson; 99C1713 (D); Brown; 5/13/99
- Tools for Schools Project, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH Indoor Air Quality- Wilson Central, 98C1713 (e), Brown, 2/17/99, (coord. Train the trainer)
- Tech Assist- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH- Tools for Schools (Walk thru/Data Rpt) Wilson, 99C1713 F, Brown, 4/26/99
- Tech Assist- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH- Tools for Schools (Tech Rpt) Wilson, 99C1713 G, Brown, 4/20/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Buy-in Mtg.), 98C1714 (a), Brown, 1/6 and 3/16/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Data Analysis), 98C1714 (b), Brown, 1/24-3/6/00
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Write Tech Rpt), 98C1714 (c), Brown, 3/16/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Follow-up), 98C1714 (d), Brown, 3/16/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Coord. Train the trainer), 98C1714 (e), Brown, 4/26/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Data Review and Walkthru), 98C1714 (f), Brown, 6/7/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH- Waterfront School (Tech Report), 98C1714 (g), Brown, 3/16/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH- Bennett Park Mont. School (Train the Trainer), 98C1715 (e), Brown, 6/10/99
- Tools for Schools (Walk-thru), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, 99C1715 (f), Brown, 10/04/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Buy-in-Mtg.), 98C1716 (a), Brown, 1/11/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Data Analysis), 99C1716 B, Brown, 3/1/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Tech Rpt), 99C1716 C, Brown, [Cancelled]
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Follow-up), 99C1716 D, Brown, [Cancelled]
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint (Train the Trainer), 99C1716 E, Brown, 3/4/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Train the Trainer), 99C1716 E, Brown, 3/4/99
- Indoor Air Quality Tech Assist, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Data Rvw/Walkthru), 99C1716 F, Brown, 6/4/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint (Tech Report), 99C1716 G, Brown, 8/31/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint (Presentation), 99C1716 H, Brown, 9/7/99
- Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH- Starpoint School (Presentation), 99C1716 I, Brown, 9/7/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality (Data Analysis), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Salamanca School District (Salamanca, NY), 98C1717 (b), Brown, 4/23/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality (Write Tech. Rept), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Salamanca School District, 98C1717 (c), Brown, 4/05/99
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality (Followup), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Salamanca School District, 98C1717 (d), Brown
- Indoor Air Quality (Train the trainer), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Salamanca School District, 98C1717 (e), Brown
- Indoor Air Quality (Data Rvw and Walkthru), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Salamanca School District, 98C1717 (f), Brown
- Tech Assist: Indoor Air Quality (Tech. Report), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Salamanca School District, 98C1717 (g), Brown
- Tools for Schools (Train the Trainer), 1999 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH- Batavia Schools, 98C1718 (e), Brown, 6/8/99
- Tech Assist- Quality Mkt-Field Investigation, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  UFCW Local 1, 98C1719, Brown, 8/21/98- 2/15/99
- No. 1723 (A): Indoor Air Quality, Albion Correctional Facility, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- No. 1723 (A): Indoor Air Quality, Albion Correctional Facility, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- No. 1725: Crowley v. C-E Minerals, 1998-2006 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- No. 1725: Crowley v. C-E Minerals, 1998-2006 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- No. 1725: Crowley v. C-E Minerals, 1998-2006 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- SH 1757, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Client: ALCOSH, Title: Tech Asst.- Benzene and Leukemia
- Health and Safety-Comp. Work Station- Deni Insurance, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  98C1784, Brown, 11/5/98
- Occup. History and Medical Surveillance- Paul W. Beltz, PC (Box 4, Folder 48)
  98C1787, Brown, [cancelled]
- Tech Assist.-Dermatitis, Curtis Screw Company, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  98C1792, Brown, 11/19-12/11/99
- SH 1801 Court Case, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Tech Asst.- Indoor Air Qual. (Site Visit/Report), 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Salamanca School District- ALCOSH, 98C1802+1807 (a), Brown, 12/1-12/4/98 and 1/29/99
- No. 1803: Indoor Air Quality, Starpoint School District, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- No. 1803: Indoor Air Quality, Starpoint School District, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- No. 1803: Indoor Air Quality, Starpoint School District, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- No. 1803: Indoor Air Quality, Starpoint School District, 1989-1999 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Indoor Air Quality in Schools, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  NYSUT, 98C1804, Brown, 5/15/99
- SH 1807, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  98C1807, Title: Tech Asst.
- Tech Asst: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  NYSUT- North Tonawanda High School, 98C1808, Brown, 3/5-6/30/99
- Tech Asst: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  NYSUT/School #29 (Rochester), 98C1834, Brown, 3/19/99
- Tech Asst: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  WNYCOSH- UCPA/UCPEU, 98C1857, Brown
- Tech Asst: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  NYSUT, 98C1858, Brown
- Tech Asst: Indoor Air Quality, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  NYSUT/School #5 (Rochester), 98C1859, Brown, 3/29/99
- No. 1862: Lung Case, Paul Beltz (was 1097, 794), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- No. 1862: Lung Case, Paul Beltz (was 1097, 794), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- No. 1862: Lung Case, Paul Beltz (was 1097, 794), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- No. 1862: Lung Case, Paul Beltz (was 1097, 794), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- No. 1862: Lung Case, Paul Beltz (was 1097, 794), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- No. 1862: Lung Case, Paul Beltz (was 1097, 794), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bloodborne Pathogen Train-the-Trainer, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  ALCOSH, 99C1929, Brown, 2/9/2000
- Hazard Communication Train-the-Trainer, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  ALCOSH- Jamestown, 99C1930, Brown, 11/17/99 [cancelled]
- W/P Violence Trng, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  ALCOSH- Silver Creek- Village, 99C1931, Brown, 10/14/99
- No. 1932: Indoor Air Quality, Phillips Lytle, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- No. 1932: Indoor Air Quality, Phillips Lytle, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- No. 1932: Indoor Air Quality, Phillips Lytle, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- No. 1932: Indoor Air Quality, Phillips Lytle, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 99C1972, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Indoor Air Quality (Tech Asst), 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  NYSUT/Jefferson Elem. School, 99C1973, Brown, 6/11-6/28/00
- Train the Trainer, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH- Fedco, 00C2069, Brown, 7/13/00
- Tech Asst: IAQ, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  SweetHome Central School District, 99C2070, Brown, 1/27 and 2/8/00
- Environmental Action Guide, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Healthy Schools Network A and B, 00C2142, Brown, 7/1/00
- No. 2143: Job Hazard Analysis, Monroe County Water Authority, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- No. 2143: Job Hazard Analysis, Monroe County Water Authority, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- No. 2143: Job Hazard Analysis, Monroe County Water Authority, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Vesuvius, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  00C2154
- Indoor Air Quality, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH/NYS Assoc. of School Admin., 00C2172, Brown, 11/17/00
- Indoor Air Quality, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  BFI, Inc. Waste Systems, 00C2173 A+B, Brown, 9/7/00
- USEPA- Tools for Schools, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH- Webster Schools, 00C2186
- USEPA- Tools for Schools, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH- Webster Schools- DeWitt, 00C2187 and 01C2187
- USEPA- Tools for Schools, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH- Webster Schools- SPRY, 00C2188 and 01C2188
- USEPA- Tools for Schools, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH- Webster Schools- WHS, 00C2189 and 01C2189
- #2189, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Salamanca- IAQ (Hold)
- Akron- IAQ- Tech. Asst., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, 00C2254 and 01C2254, 03/12/01
- Wilson School- IAQ, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #2282, 03/29/01
- Williamsville School District- IAQ, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #2329, 06/04/01
- Tech. Asst., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Paul Beltz, Assoc., #2340
- Tech. Asst., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  UCPA, #2341, 05/08/01
- Barker Schools, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Tech. Asst., #2342, 05/17/01
- Cayuga Heights Elem. School, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  02C2356
- Ventilation at Trek, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #2357, 08/09/01
- Wilson Schools- Tech. Asst., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #2360, 07/09/01
- No. 2364: Composting, 2001-2012 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- No. 2364: Composting, 2001-2012 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- No. 2364: Composting, 2001-2012 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- NYWEA, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  #2369, 02/05/02
- IAQ, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  St. Bonaventure Friary, #2384, 10/03/01
- S.W. School Distr.- IAQ, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #2421, 11/29/01
- S.W. School Distr.- IAQ, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #2422, 12/10/01
- S.W. School Distr.- IAQ, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #2423, 12/10/01
- S.W. School Distr.- IAQ, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #2424, 01/07/02
- S.W. School Distr.- IAQ, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #2425, 01/07/02
- S.W. School Distr.- IAQ, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, 02C and 01C #2426
- No. 2447: Chemical Hazard Communication, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- No. 2447: Chemical Hazard Communication, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- No. 2447: Chemical Hazard Communication, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Resp. Prot.- Trek, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  ROCOSH, #2448, 01/16/02
- Crisis Prev., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Greater Bflo. Env. Confer., #2452, 5/21/02
- Riplex- Site Inv., 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, 01C and 02C #2453
- Workplace Violence Confer. (Ithaca), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Tompkins Cty. Coalition, #2458, 04/04/02
- MWF's, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  UTC/Carried, #2463, 01/18/02
- Lead R+R, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  NYCHPD, #2464, 1/22/02
- Lead R+R- Trainer, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  NYCHPD, #2465, 01/23/02
- No. 2466: Safe Work Practices, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- No. 2466: Safe Work Practices, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Lead R+R Trainer, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  NYCHPD, #2467, 1/25/02
- W/WW H&S, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  NYS Thruway Authority, 01C #2468, 04/10/02
- Crisis Mgmt- Water/WWTP's, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #2649, 03/26/02
- MWFs, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  UTC, 01C #2470, 01/18/02
- MWFs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  UTC, #2471, 01/18/02
- MWFs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  UTC, 01C#2472, 01/18/02
- SHRM Module- Health, Safety, and Security, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Cornell, #2473, 03/25/02; Contains Unlabeled Sony CD-R and SHRM Module 6 Book
- IAQ, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #2474, 03/11/02
- IAQ, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #2475, 03/21/02
- IAQ- Webster, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #2476, 02/27/02
- IAQ- Webster, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #2477, 02/27/02
- IAQ- Webster, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH- 01/02, #2478, 03/06/02
- IAQ- Webster, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #2479, 03/18/02
- IAQ- Webster, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2480, 03/20/02
- MWFs and IAQ, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  NYUCOEM, 01C#2481, 4/27/02
- Hartland Hwy, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #2482, 02/14/02
- Hartland Hwy- Conf. Speaker, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #2483, 04/19/02
- Jounal Article about "Perspectives at Work", 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  01C#2484
- Lead Insp., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Adelaide Assoc, #2485, 1/29/02
- FF's- BBP/Hazcom, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2486, 03/01/02
- FF's- Hazcom/BBPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2487, 03/01/02
- FF's- Hazcom/BBPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2488, 03/28/02
- FF's- Hazcom/BBPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2489, 03/28/02
- FF's- Stress, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2490, 05/07/02
- FF's- Stress, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2491, 05/07/02
- FF's- Stress, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2492, 05/28/02
- FF's- Stress, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, 01C#2493, 05/28/02
- Museum Assoc. of NY, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  01C#2494, 04/30/02
- VA- Confer., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  Crisis Mgmt. (Proposal), #2495
- Viol., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  NYSPEF, 01C#2496, 03/20/02
- Stress, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  NYSPEF, 01C#2497, 03/20/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2498, 02/19/02
- Lead SWPs- Trainer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2499, 02/20/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2500, 02/21/02
- Lead SWPs- Trainer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2501, 02/22/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2502, 02/28/02
- Lead SWPs- Trainer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2503, 02/26/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2504, 02/27/02
- Lead SWPs- Trainer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2505, 02/28/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2506, 03/05/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2507, 03/06/02
- Lead SWPs, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2508, 03/07/02
- Lead SWPs- Trainer, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  NYCHPD, 01C#2509, 03/08/02
- Revise Factsheets, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  Cornell- P.ED., 01C#2510, 02/14/02
- IAQ, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  Lorman, 02C#2511, 07/09/02
- Strategies for Teaching H and S, MI, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 42)